thatagency.com 2019-05-08

# Website Privacy Policy | THAT Agency

Open Policy on the Issue of Privacy: We at THAT Agency adhere to a strict professional code of ethical conduct in the handling of your personal information. Read below to review how we safeguard your relationship with us.

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the THATAgency.com website whether from customers or prospects. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Credit Card Information

### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order, to contact you with regard to your order, to respond to email inquires, to participate in chat room discussions, or to send an email newsletter. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
